{
    "1": {"question": "According to forklore, what legendary creature creates no reflection in a mirror?", "answers": ["Unicorn", "Valkyrie", "Medusa", "Vampire"], "correct": 4},
    "2": {"question": "What is the capital of France?", "answers": ["Lion", "Marseille", "Paris", "Montpellier"], "correct": 3},
    "3": {"question": "A traditional 'Hawaiian' pizza is topped with an unusual combination of pineapple and what?", "answers": ["Bacon", "Ham", "Cheddar", "Tomatoes"], "correct": 2},
    "4": {"question": "How many horns does a unicorn, a ram, and a triceratops have altogether?", "answers": ["4", "5", "7", "6"], "correct": 4},
    "5": {"question": "A web site that doesn't allow access to a page will often prompt the phrase 'Forbidden' and what code number?", "answers": ["403", "404", "500", "400"], "correct": 1},
    "6": {"question": "A rich old man who is married to a young, attractive woman is often described as a what?", "answers": ["Iossy", "Sugar Daddy", "Sugar Father", "Prime Minister"], "correct": 2},
    "7": {"question": "According to Greek myth, King Midas had the power to turn everything he touched into what?", "answers": ["Silver", "Gold", "Glass", "Blood"], "correct": 2},
    "8": {"question": "According to myth, what countrys capital was founded by the twins Romulus and Remus?", "answers": ["Greenland", "Rome", "Italy", "Zimbabwe"], "correct": 3},
    "9": {"question": "After Russia, what is the largest country in the world by land area?", "answers": ["United States", "Antarctica", "Canada", "China"], "correct": 3},
    "10": {"question": "Which letter represents infinity in advanced mathematics?", "answers": ["Ash", "Eight", "Omega", "Aleph"], "correct": 4},
    "11": {"question": "How many months have 28 days?", "answers": ["1", "8", "2", "12"], "correct": 4},
    "12": {"question": "Boasting of its environmental consciousness, what retailer states that the two colors in its logo blend to make green?", "answers": ["Ikea", "Coca-Cola", "FedEx", "McDonalds"], "correct": 1},
    "13": {"question": "When did the USSR collapse?", "answers": ["1898", "1991", "2000", "1987"], "correct": 2},
    "14": {"question": "In Cards Against Humanity, the person reading the black card is called what?", "answers": ["Marker", "Card reader", "Tzar", "Humanity"], "correct": 3},
    "15": {"question": "How many numbers between ten and twenty have names that end with the suffix '-teen?'", "answers": ["8", "7", "20", "5"], "correct": 2},
    "16": {"question": "According to the famous superstition, what should you do before leaving for a trip?", "answers": ["Smile to yourself in the mirror", "Spit three times", "Sit down", "smoke a pipe"], "correct": 3},
    "17": {"question": "How tall was the first programmable, electronic, general-purpose digital computer, ENIAC?", "answers": ["30m", "10m", "2m", "120m"], "correct": 1},
    "18": {"question": "How do you win at a Russian Roulette?", "answers": ["By letting the other person go first", "By having the other person die", "By not dying", "By not playing"], "correct": 4},
    "19": {"question": "According to Joules Vernes popular book, who was Nemo?", "answers": ["A fish", "A submarine captain", "A US persident", "Harel Asher"], "correct": 2},
    "20": {"question": "The cry 'eureka!' comes from a Greek word meaning 'I have' what?", "answers": ["Killed it", "Dyed it", "Found it", "Done it"], "correct": 3}
}